原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译     千只鹤飞过波千鸟
翻译     tong大梨  屯栗子  五天
校对     屯栗子
时间轴     蒜头
后期     渔夫
总监     屯栗子
辛普森一家
第三十一季  第二集
生日快乐  莱尼
莱尼肯定大吃一惊
Oh, boy, Lenny is gonna be so surprised.
而我有最合适的贺卡
And I got the perfect card.
生日快乐  老朋友
可以
Yeah.
山上总比山下好
您已出份子钱  请签名
Having chipped in, you may now sign.
干得漂亮
Nice work.
不写"祝一切都好"  我欣赏这种克制
No "Best wishes," I like the restraint.
我想过写"致意"  但莱尼懂我的感受
Yeah, I thought about "Regards," But Lenny knows how I feel.
好了各位  安静
Okay, everybody, be quiet.
莱尼随时会来
Lenny's gonna be here any minute. Shh.
派对基金
惊  喜
Sur... prise.
我以为这是输血室
I thought this was my blood transfusion room,
但是好像这里没有小宝宝
but, uh, there's not a baby in sight.
这是个给莱尼的惊喜派对  先生
It's a surprise party for Lenny, sir.
每个人都付了五块钱  用来买贺卡和蛋糕
Everybody chipped in five bucks for a card and a cake
及请近距离魔术师胡言乱语先生现场表演
and a show by close-up magician Abraca-Debra.
什么  该死
What? Damn!
既然如此  我想我也应该签名
Well, in that case, I suppose I should sign, too.
"致以诚挚的问候  查尔斯·蒙哥马利·伯恩斯"
"With regards, C. Montgomery Burns."
莱尼  祝你生日快乐
Ah, Lenny, happy birthday.
生日快乐  莱尼
致以诚挚的问候
查尔斯·蒙哥马利·伯恩斯
生日快乐  老朋友
这是有史以来最棒的生日
This is the greatest birthday ever!
最妙的是  伯恩斯先生在我的贺卡上签了名
And best of all, Mr. Burns signed my card.
敬所有出份子钱的人
To everyone who chipped in.
份子钱  份子钱
Chipped in. Chipped in.
份子钱
Chipped in.
什么样的人会在生日贺卡上签名
What kind of person signs a birthday card
但是不出份子钱的
and doesn't chip in?
你签名  你出份子钱
You sign the card, you got to chip in.
-这就是贺卡签名的原则  -他签了多大
- It's the code of the card. - How big did he sign?
艾迪堡那么大
Eddie Bauer big.
不出钱的傻缺签名
Stupid unpaid signature.
这是一个核电厂所能发生的
This is the worst thing that ever happened
最糟糕的事情
at a nuclear power plant.
侯默  别想了
Homie, just let it go.
别被一个签名逼疯了
Don't let a signature drive you crazy.
你说得对  亲爱的
You're right, honey.
我不管了
I'll let it go.
真不知道没了你我该怎么办
I don't know what I'd do without you.
查尔斯·蒙哥马利·伯恩斯
生日快乐  莱尼
Happy birthday, Lenny.
不  不
No. No!
不
No!
侯默  怎么了
Homie, what is it?
我做了最可怕的噩梦
I had the most horrible nightmare
就在我听了你的建议之后
where I listened to your advice.
春田核电厂
好了  可以的
Okay, okay.
可以的侯默  你行的
Okay, Homer, you can do this.
你可以把事情做好的
You can make things right.
伯恩斯先生  每个在贺卡上
Mr. Burns, everyone who signed
签名的人都出了份子钱  除了你
that birthday card chipped in except for you.
你欠了五块钱
You owe five dollars.
你竟敢
How dare you...
这么担心
give that the slightest worry.
希望你睡得安稳
Hope you didn't lose any sleep
没被这小误会打扰
over this little misunderstanding.
给  穿了线的蟋蟀代表好运
Here, have a cricket on a thread for good luck.
你这个禽兽
You monster...
占老年人的便宜
taking advantage of an old man.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
伯恩斯先生正在进行
Mr. Burns is heavily medicated
皮肤浓缩机的强烈全天候治疗
on a round-the-clock regimen of skin thickeners.
治疗的副作用是
The side effect of that medication
表现出多次无法控制的合"礼"行为
is bouts of uncontrollable decency.
而你利用了这一点
And you exploited that.
我要把你降职到这里最差的工作
I'm demoting you to the worst job in this place:
监督辅导核电厂的实习生们
supervising the nuclear plant interns.
听好了千禧一代  我是侯默·辛普森
Listen up, millenniums. I'm Homer Simpson,
你们的新监督员
your new supervisor.
所以别再玩阅后即焚  堡垒游戏
So stop Snapchatting, Fortnite-ing
或是不付优步账单了
and swiping right on your Uber Venmos.
我们其实是在复现核电厂启动序列
We're actually replicating plant start-up sequences
模拟高需求能量缩裂的效果
to simulate the effects of high-demand energy draws.
污染物和辐射量的关系
Contamination versus irradiation--
你有何想法
your thoughts?
处理反应速率
Address rate of reaction.
我们可以设想什么变量
What variables can we assume?
他的脑子密度比锇188还要大
This guy is denser than osmium-188.
我真的没听错吗
Are my ears hearing this?
你们真的在嘲笑侯默·杰·辛普森
Are you seriously busting the clangers
犯下的荒唐的错误吗
of Homer J. Simpsons?
他是神  他的错误是不可嘲笑的
This man is a god and his clangers are unbustable.
你们现在看到的是7G区的
You're looking at the Michael Jordan
迈克尔·乔丹
of Sector 7G.
而你们的嘲笑也无法抵消他的功绩
And you humps aren't worthy to swill his backwash.
你在支持我
You're sticking up for me?
你是谁
Who are you?
迈克·韦格曼  核电厂实习生
Mike Wegman, nuclear intern.
我是你的头号粉丝
And your number one fan.
你的英雄的手机套里
Yeah, well, your hero has a Pop-Tart
有一个果馅饼
in his cell phone holster.
逗我呢
Are you kidding?
没有人可以不尊敬侯默·杰·辛普森
No one disrespects Homer Simpsons.
你不可以  里奇  不就有个站立式办公桌
Not you, Ricky, with your standing desk.
这可不能健身  研究早就证明过了
It's not a workout; it's been disproven.
你也不行  格里琴
And not you, Gretchen,
从瓶子里直接喝咖啡奶精的怪人
drinking coffee creamer straight from the bottle.
你个奇怪的意大利人
You exude amaretto, you freak.
还有本杰明  没有人会在
And, Benjamin, no one ever got trampled
麦可·布雷音乐会上被踩踏
at a Michael Bublé concert.
放弃你的诉讼吧  把法律系统都堵塞了
Drop the friggin' lawsuit, you're clogging up the system.
这个人是个榜样
This man is a dynamo.
你们这些小杂碎都给我放尊重点
So you shaved coconuts give him your full respect.
好吧好吧  对不起  辛普森先生
All right, all right. Sorry, Mr. Simpson.
希望向您学习  辛普森先生
Looking forward to learning from you, Mr. Simpson.
单位里的人通常都是朝我吼  不会替我吼回去
People at work usually yell at me, not for me.
你怎么知道我是什么人的
How do you know who I am?
太谦虚了  真是个好榜样
So modest. What a dynamo.
因为这个
Because of this.
第十核电站的员工险被熔化
不管有什么麻烦事
Whenever there's trouble,
你都是整个行动的核心
you are at the heart of the action.
六号堆就是那些马变秃的原因
Number six is why all those horses went bald.
我已经仰望你很久了
Yeah. Well, I-I-I've been looking up to you for so long
现在终于见到你了
from the cheap seats, and now we're finally face-to-face,
不敢相信我真要这么说  但是我要问
I can't believe I'm saying this, but I got to ask,
你愿意指导我吗  做我的老师
w-will you be my coach? My sensei?
侯默·杰·辛普森  你愿意做我的导师吗
Homer J. Simpsons, will you be my mentor?
如果你接受  就请你
If you accept, let me know
接受这半块能量棒
by taking this half a PowerBar.
我包的很严实  没有口袋里的碎屑
I rolled up the wrapper really good so there's no pocket lint.
迈克·韦格曼斯  我愿意做你的导师
Mike Wegmans, I will be your mentor.
科斯汀顿商场
哪条领带更适合
Okay, which of these ties is better
做导师的第一天戴
for my first day as a mentor?
紫色条纹还是这个
Purple stripes or this one?
导师
你喷了我的香水吗
Are you wearing my perfume?
我喜欢你身上这个味道  他也会喜欢我身上有
I like it on you, he'll like it on me.
爸爸  这可不常见  你居然
Dad, it's not often that you--
我该怎么说
how do I put this?--
这么在乎你的工作
care so much about your job?
现在我可是导师了  一切都变了
Well, now that I'm a mentor, everything's changed.
这是第一次  有一个活生生的人
For the first time, another human being
需要依赖我来指导他度过余生
is dependent on me to guide them through life.
我指导的这个人非常酷
This guy I'm menting is so cool.
听人讲话的时候嘴巴会惊讶地张开
He listens with his mouth open.
他在推特上被很多名人都拉黑了
He's been blocked by so many celebrities on Twitter.
他还认为我是整个核电站里
And he thinks I'm the most valuable worker
最有价值的员工
at the entire nuclear plant.
我懂了
Oh, I get it.
他蠢到家了
He's super dumb.
随便你怎么嘲笑
Mock all you want.
在单位里终于有人崇拜我了
I finally have someone at work who admires me.
他好胖
He's fat.
侯默  你的裤子
Homer, your pants.
他们还会再回来的
They'll come around again.
一直都这样
They always do.
春田核电站
我优秀的老师来了
There's my thoroughbred.
我按照你的喜好买了咖啡
I-I got your coffee just the way you like it.
没有咖啡  只有甜甜圈球
No coffee, just doughnut holes.
7G区
天哪  我的老天鹅啊
Oh, my God, are you busting my bricks?
这是真的吗
I-Is this real?
传说中的7G区
Sector 7G.
7G  一个连奥林匹斯诸神都不敢涉足的地方
7G, where Olympus fears to tread.
那是当然
He sure does.
你的知识堪比五级飓风
Okay, you are a category five hurricane of knowledge,
与你相比  我就像是井底之蛙
and I'm like that old idiot who won't leave his beach house.
用你的知识把我淹没在我的小阁楼里吧
Please, drown me in my attic with what you know.
我就知道你会这么说
I thought you might say that.
所以我准备了鸡汤海报
So I've prepared inspirational posters.
要么做大  要么回家
赌上你自己
感觉就像是阿玛雷·斯塔德迈尔
I feel like Amar'e Stoudemire
第一次踏足耶路撒冷
when he first set foot in Jerusalem.
还有什么
W-What else you got?
我来看看
Uh, let's see...
-不要忘了  -对对对对对对对
- Don't forget about the, uh... - Y-Y-Y-Y-Y-Yeah.
-那个  还有  -金句
- Oh, uh, and, of course, - Gold.
-你需要  你只要  -金句  好的
- you got to, you just got to. - Gold. Okay.
-因为如果你不  -沉浸在金句的海洋里
- Because if you don't... - Soakin' it in. Gold.
-那个  -沉浸其中
- Well, oh. - Soakin' it in.
-其实他们已经没有了  -我能记住
- Well, they don't have that anymore. - I can remember this.
-看见这些了吗  -嗯
- And you see these? - Yeah.
-我过一阵再跟你说  -好好好好好好好
- I'm gonna tell you that later. - Y-Y-Y-Y-Y-Yeah.
我简直不敢相信
I can't believe this.
我才35岁  我就坐在了
I-I'm only 35 and I am sitting at the feet
原子版巴巴布伊面前[形容领域大咖]
of the atomic Baba Booey.
你35岁了
You're 35?
那你为什么干着二十岁的人做的工作
Then why do you have a job of a 20-year-old
说话像个十岁的孩子
and talk like a ten-year-old?
是这样的
Here's how it is.
我和我兄弟内斯托
So, my buddy 'Nesto and me
我们清理排水管挣钱
were cleaning gutters for cash,
然后那个废物掉下来了
when that idiot 'Nesto falls off
掉在了狗窝上  愚蠢的内斯托
and lands on a doghouse. Stupid 'Nesto.
然后我父母就开始专心帮我寻找职业方向了
Then my parents are on my case to get a real career,
一些更实际的东西[离地面更近]
something "closer to the ground."
我就想  为什么不追随着我的英雄
So I thought, "Why not follow my hero
从事人类最伟大的行业
"into man's greatest calling?
核能什么的
Nuclear whatever."
所以我到核电站去
So I went down to the plant,
跟他们说我算是土著人
told them I was part Native American--
我有可能是  我一直都像他们一样
I could be, I always liked those guys--
然后  我就变成实习生了
and boom! I'm an intern.
短短三年之后  我就有导师了
Three short years later, got myself a mentor.
我的海报真的起作用了了
Wow. My posters really worked.
但是根本不用我来告诉你你有多优秀
But you don't need me telling you how great you are,
你在家里听的就够多的了
y-you get enough of that at home.
生日快乐  莱尼
Happy birthday, Lenny.
查尔斯·蒙哥马利·伯恩斯
那个  迈克
Say, Mike,
不如你来我家吃个晚饭吧
why don't you come over to my house for dinner?
我想把你在我身边的相处方式
I've got some people I'd like to introduce
介绍给他们看看
to the way you act around me.
好  我可以
Okay. I-I could do that.
我做得到
I could make that happen.
我可以的
Huh. I got this.
莱尼  你个鸭子嘴神经病
Hey, Lenny, you duck-faced psycho,
猜猜谁要去辛普森家里吃饭了  我
guess who's going to Homer Simpson's house for a meal? Me.
我是卡尔
Uh, I'm Carl.
我希望你请学生来家里吃饭之前
I wish you would give me more of a heads-up
能早点告诉我
before inviting a mentee for dinner.
要是在砂锅菜上多加一倍薯片
I guess we'll have enough
我们应该够吃
if I double the chip layer on the casserole.
别担心  你肯定会喜欢这孩子的
Don't worry, you're gonna love this kid.
孩子  他看着四十多了
Kid? He looks 40-plus.
侯默  她真美
Oh, Homer, she is a beaut.
我算知道你上班总打盹的原因了
Now I know why you're always napping at work.
果然是"铲雪先生"
Mr. Plow, indeed.
《辛普森一家》第四季第九集侯默的称呼
你好  我叫马姬
Hello. I'm Marge.
我叫迈克·韦格曼斯  她是莫琳
Mike Wegman. This is Maureen.
里面这位叫帕特里珂·尤因·韦格曼斯
And this is Patrick Ewing Wegman.
源自前美国职业篮球运动员帕特里克·尤因
她是女孩  别叫她帕特里珂
It's a girl. You can't name her Patrick.
场均永远二点四次盖帽
2.4 blocks per game, lifetime.
她就叫帕特里珂
She's Patrick.
看看这桌饭
Look at this spread.
我还以为会是  聚会式快餐
I-I was expecting, like, a-a party sub,
但热萝卜  谁的奇思妙想
but hot carrots? Who thinks of that?
慢点吃  你又得烫了嘴
Slow it, you'll burn your mouth again.
知道了  我吹吹
All right, all right, I'm gonna blow on 'em.
谢谢你们的款待
Thank you for having us.
迈克非常崇拜您的丈夫
Mike admires your husband so much.
听到了没  "非常"
Do you hear that? "So much"!
我家人从来没崇拜过我
They don't admire me any much.
你得抓牢他  马姬
You better hold on to this guy, Marge,
如果他是单身  他会抢手到被生吞活剥
'cause if he were single, he'd be cleaning up.
生吞活剥  骨头不剩
I mean cleaning up, knee-deep.
别担心  亲爱的
Don't worry, honey.
记住你是我的唯一
You're the only woman for me.
我没担心
I wasn't worried.
韦格曼夫人  你俩怎么认识的
So, Mrs. Wegman, how did you two meet?
你会喜欢这故事的
Oh, well, you're gonna love this story.
很浪漫  告诉她  亲爱的
It's so romantic. Tell her, honey.
说吧
Go ahead, tell her.
我婚礼他是服务生
He was a waiter at my wedding.
她那么美  就像《明星伙伴》里
She was so beautiful, like one of those girls
HBO喜剧
那些默默走出文尼卧室的女孩中的
you see leaving Vinny's bedroom on Entourage
其中一个
that don't say nothin'.
迈克  你一幅聪明样
So, Mike, you seem like a sharp tack.
我爸爸能教你什么呢
What exactly is my dad teaching you?
打盹时怎么吃甜甜圈吗
How to eat doughnuts while napping?
我没听错这小崽子刚说的话吧
Did this little hump just say what I thought I heard?
没关系迈克  我不在乎
It's okay, Mike. I don't sweat it.
是啊迈克  侯默唯一在乎的就是肉汁
Yeah, Mike, the only thing Homer sweats is gravy.
没有人可以不尊敬侯默·杰·辛普森
No one disrespects Homer Simpsons!
尤其你这种又丑又无知的小年轻
Especially not an ugly little punk like you.
没错  我说"丑"
That's right, I said "Ugly."
你那颗头就像不情愿的提线木偶
Your head looks like a rejected Muppet.
两个高尔夫球粘在一个燕麦罐上
Two golf balls glued to a can of oats.
在你那汤米·拉索达肚子和牙签腿之间
Between that Tommy Lasorda gut and those toothpick legs,
你不是孩子  而是行走的土豆钟
you are not a kid-- you are a walkin' potato clock.
哈哈哈  丑  哈
Ha-ha-ha! Ugly! Ha!
提线木偶
Muppet...
牙签腿
Ah! Toothpick legs!
土豆钟
Potato clock!
我就想听听你的滴答[抽泣]声  孩子
I'm just bustin' your clangers, kid.
没事了  没事的
All right, it's okay.
请你们出去
I want you out!
抱歉  非常抱歉
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
肚里的娃出生地登记在哪了
Where's the baby registered?!
霓虹之王[社交游戏公司]
DraftKings!
我得跟你道歉多少次啊
How many times do I have to say I'm sorry?
一次就够了
Once would be nice.
你可真是要把我弄哭了
Wow, you're really bustin' my clangers.
那家伙是个疯子
That guy's a lunatic.
他不是疯
He's not crazy.
他是唯一尊敬我的人
He's the only one that respects me!
孩子和我都尊敬你
The kids and I respect you.
你们只是在爱我
All you guys ever did was love me.
但看着我的眼睛说你尊敬我
But look me in the eyes and tell me you respect me,
作为一个核能系统的职工
as a nuclear guy.
我只是喜欢那种感觉
I just liked the feeling
有人能认真赞赏我的能力
that one person thinks I'm good at something.
我懂了  侯默
Mm, I get it, Homie.
但如果你真想帮一个人
But if you really want to help this guy,
要帮他成长
help him grow up.
拜托  福德姆
Come on, Fordham,
巴克内尔防守没跟上
Bucknell's got no rim protection.
他们太垃圾了  别输4分以上啊
They're garbage. Just cover the spread.
侯默  你好吗
Hey, Homer. How's it clangin'?
我在听大学篮球赛赛况
I'm, uh, just tunin' in to a little college hoops.
迈克  我在想
Yeah, Mike, I was thinking,
假设你不是一个三十五岁的
if you weren't a 35-year-old unpaid intern
无薪实习生加准爸爸  你有其他梦想吗
with a baby on the way, do you have any other dreams?
您现在正在深入指导我
Ah, man, you are mentoring me hard right now.
好  我会说的  但你别笑
Oh, okay, I'm gonna tell you, but don't laugh.
我不会的
I won't.
披萨片
Slices.
吃片披萨是最幸福的事了  对吗
Nothing better than getting a slice of pizza, right?
但披萨总会被食品保温加热灯烤干
But it's always been under the heat lamp all dried out.
该死的加热灯
Damn heat lamp.
那为什么不索性把披萨做成单块
Right. So why not make the pizza one slice at a time,
保证热度和新鲜度
hot and fresh?
每块披萨都是德瑞克·基特
Every slice is Derek Jeter.
美国职棒大联盟的选手
没有一块是斯科特·布罗修斯
No Scott Brosius in the bunch.
天才啊
That's genius!
天呐  你竟然喜欢这主意
Oh, my God, I can't believe you like it.
迈克  知道你该为这个起什么名吗
Mike! You know what you should call your slices?
迈克家披萨片
Mike's Slices.
我叫迈克
I'm Mike!
没错  你需要的是一个投资人
Yeah! Okay, what you need is an investor,
我有个完美人选
and I know the perfect person.
他给了我五块钱
He gave me five dollars.
迈克家披萨片
每块都是新鲜出炉
Every slice hot and fresh
从烤箱直达嘴巴
from the oven into your mouth.
每块都是基特
Every slice a Jeter.
而非斯科特·布罗修斯
No Scott Brosiuses.
我为什么不点个披萨饼自己分
Why can't I get a whole pizza and slice it myself?
根本没有披萨饼这一说
There are no whole pizzas.
迈克家披萨片
只有片的  新鲜出炉
It's just slices, hot and fresh.
别担心您的投资  伯恩斯先生
And don't worry about investing with this guy, Mr. Burns,
因为我  侯默·杰·辛普森
because he's backed by the full mentorship
是他的全职导师
of Homer J. Simpsons.
我很荣幸的告诉你们
Then it's my pleasure to tell you...
这是我听过的最蠢的点子
that that is the stupidest idea I've ever heard.
把这实习生带出去吧  你个傻子
Get this intern out of my office, you nincompoop!
没有人可以不尊敬侯默·杰·辛普森
Ho! No one disrespects Homer J. Simpsons.
迈克  别这样
No, Mike, don't.
傻
Nin...
子
com... poop!
听着  你这个脑满善存银片的混账
Listen to me, you skunk-bag full of Centrum Silver
把装满花生碎的大屁股往那里一坐
sitting on your peanut brittle ass
长着一张跨世纪的秃鹰丑脸
with your turn-of-the-century buzzard face.
根本不配戳这人的脊梁骨
You ain't worthy to squeegee this man's back sweat.
你身上的味道好像被人丢在空心南瓜灯里的
You smell like Chinese food that someone left
中餐的味道
in an old jack-o'-lantern.
我的导师是整个扎莱斯最闪亮的那颗钻石
My mentor is the shiniest diamond in the whole Zales,
所以把你的这些器官塞回福尔马林里去
so stuff your organs back in their jars
趴回你老母亲的子宫里
and crawl in your mummy box,
你这个病态的  长满霉菌的  丙型肝炎吸血鬼
you sick, fungused-up, hep-C Dracula!
对了  他已经停了快乐药片了
By the way, he's off his happy pills.
你很幸运  伯恩斯先生的枪已经200岁了
You're lucky Mr. Burns gun was 200 years old.
没错  但现在我的医生说
Yeah, but now my doctor says
我的脸不能再承受一击了
I can't get shot in the face again.
现在谁最丑啊  小脑袋
Who's ugly now, pellet-head?
好了  没事  别哭
Come on, it's okay. Don't cry.
我没哭  这些BB弹害我脑袋很沉重
I'm not. All the BBs in my head are making it heavy.
迈克  都是我的错
Mike, this is all my fault.
我知道你觉得我是个很棒的核能人  但我不是
I know you think I'm a great nuclear guy, but I'm not.
不是我阻止了这些事故
I didn't stop those accidents.
这都是我引起的
I caused them.
什么  不是
Huh? No. No.
我所有的海报  "赌上你自己"
All my posters-- "Bet on Yourself,"
"要么做大  要么回家"
"Go Big or Go Home"--
是我在海报店偷东西被抓住了
I was caught shoplifting those from a poster store.
我是想做大事  但做完他们不让我回家
I was trying to go big, and they wouldn't let me go home.
迈克  面对事实吧  我是个糟糕的导师
Mike, face it, I'm a bad mentor.
没有人可以不尊敬侯默·杰·辛普森
No one disrespects Homer Simpsons.
你也不行
Not even you.
像我这样睡别人新娘的混蛋  你这样的导师
You're the best mentor a lousy bride-banger like me
是我力所能及范围内最好的
could ever ask for.
而且我要证实这个观点
And I'm gonna prove it.
谁把BB弹撒的到处都是
Who spilled BBs all over the... whoa!
导师
Yo! Mentor!
迈克家披萨片
你们谁想吃一片不是从披萨上
Anybody want a slice of pizza
切下来的披萨片
that wasn't sliced from a pizza?
你这个流动餐车哪里来的
Where'd you get a food truck?
都是因为你  导师  因为你  接受吧
It's all cause of you, mentor, all cause of you. Deal with it.
我跟孩子们要一份披萨饼
The boys and I will take a large pie.
你不识字吗  小老头
Can't you read a truck, Cookie Puss?
只有披萨片
Slices only!
好嘞  请给我三片  谢谢
All righty, three slices, please.
会在13  26  39分钟后好
They'll be ready in 13, 26 and 39 minutes.
别挡住窗户  老家伙
And don't block the window, sizzle chest.
我的那片什么时候能好
When will my slice be ready?
我说的这个片  是指你未偿贷款的
And by "Slice," I mean the first payment
第一笔还款
on your outstanding loan.
你从黑帮那里借钱
You borrowed money from the mob?!
不不不不不不  没事的
No, no, no, no, no, no. It's all good.
我从胖东尼那里借了10万美元  为期一周
I took a one-week loan from Fat Tony for a hundred grand.
我把5万买了流动餐车
I put $50k into the truck
然后把剩下的5万押在了今晚的里海比赛上
and then bet the other 50 on tonight's Lehigh game,
很保险的
which is a lock.
等我赢了赌注  我会把钱还给黑帮
So when I win the bet, I pay back the mob,
然后就能免费获得这辆流动餐车了
and I own the truck free and clear.
不是吧
Oh, no.
你赌上的是你自己
You bet on yourself!
披萨片
要么做大  要么回家  老铁
Go big or go home, baby.
里海队有麻烦了
And Lehigh's in trouble
因为圣十字队快攻拿下无人防守的20分
as Holy Cross goes on an unanswered 20-point run.
不不不  里海很保险的
No, no, no, Lehigh is a lock!
在冰球场上他们从未败过的
They're undefeated on floors with hockey ice beneath them.
因为一场爱国者联盟篮球赛
Yet again, a man's life hangs by the gossamer thread
又一个人再次命悬一线
of Patriot League basketball.
举起枪来
Guns up.
但是里海靠一个远距离投三分球
But Lehigh takes the lead with a three
暂时领先三分
from way behind the arc.
-太棒了  -放下枪
- Yes! - Guns down.
但是十字军们用关键
But the Crusaders answer
一记篮筐球挽回颓势
with a floater in the key!
里海回应了一记野兽般的暴扣
And Lehigh comes back with a monster dunk!
太棒了
Yeah!
随着比赛最后一秒的结束  里海又投入一球
As the final seconds tick away, Lehigh has this one in the bag!
但也死挺了
The body bag!
虽然经历了最后一秒的起伏
As a last-second half-court heave
十字军队获得了胜利
gives Holy Cross the win.
举起枪来
Guns up.
打开保险
Safeties off.
别担心  我知道一个地方
Don't worry, I know a place
他们绝对找不到我们
where they will never find us.
废弃场
海上救助  咆哮的狗  废料堆
快餐车废弃场
A food truck graveyard.
浪费的愤怒
为什么有这么多失败的品牌
Why are there so many failed ones?
因为他们像我一样没有原创
'Cause they don't have an original concept, like me.
侯默  我得跟你坦白一件事情
Homer, I got to tell you one thing.
你的孩子不丑
Your boy's not ugly.
他很漂亮
He's gorgeous.
像他爸爸那样
Just like his old man.
他会好起来的
He's gonna clean up.
告诉帕特里珂我爱她
Tell baby Patrick I loved her.
好了  干死我吧
All right, do me.
我闻到了马苏里拉奶酪
I smell mozzarella
慢慢在一块三角形的面团上融化的味道
gently melting over a single slice of triangular dough.
在了解之前  我们共享一个披萨饼
Before the end, we will share a pie.
只卖披萨片  你这个穴居人
It's just slices, you goombah caveman!
一般如果在加热灯下面
Mmm! Usually a slice is dried out
披萨会干掉  但这片却热乎乎新鲜极了
from sitting under a heat lamp, but this is hot and fresh!
看到了吗  这个人有很多好点子
See? This guy has good ideas.
如果...
What if...
你让迈克在流动餐车上工作还钱呢
you let Mike work in the truck to pay you back?
不行  流动餐车的生意太冒险了
No. The food truck business is too big a gamble.
随着合法网上赌博的出现
And even our gambling operation is in trouble
我们的赌博项目运行也有了麻烦
with the advent of legal online wagering.
真糟糕  你奈何不了我的流动餐车
Too bad you can't take action out of my food truck,
那么由你来下赌注吧
let the betting come to you.
现在  杀了我吧
Now, do me already!
一个可以赌博的流动餐车
A food truck that takes bets?
我要一片加奶酪
I'll take a slice of cheese
和赌乔治城的moneyline
and the moneyline on Georgetown.
东尼  我们的德育博彩非常火
Yo, Tony! We're raking it in on the sportsbook.
而且同时卖大麻也是个好选择
And it was a great idea to sell weed out of this thing also.
侯默  你相信了这个家伙
Homer, you believed in this stagelagoots
在别人不看好他时坚持己见
when no one else would.
倾听他的想法
You listened to him,
培养他的观点
nurtured his ideas,
现在他成功了
and now he is a success.
你真是个很棒的导师
Truly, you're a excellent mentor.